http://www.kushies.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
We are committed to providing our visitors with a website that respects their privacy. This website is owned and operated by KUSHIES BABY. The following privacy policy describes the information we collect and how we use it. By using this website, you consent to our privacy policy.For any questions or concerns, please contact us by email via customerservice@kushiesonline.caOr call our Toll Free telephone number (800) 841-5330; or write to us at:Kushies BabyAttention: Consumer Services / Privacy555 Barton St.Stoney Creek, ONL8E 5S1
What is Personal Information?Personal information means any information that identifies an individual. This includes information such as your name, address, telephone number, or email address. Like many websites, we gather information about how visitors use our website. In general, you can visit many of our web pages without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. We may track your Internet domain address for trends and statistics, but you will remain anonymous unless you tell us who you are. We collect information from you when you register on the site, place an order, enter a contest or sweepstakes, respond to a survey or communication such as e-mail, or participate in another site feature. When ordering or registering, we may ask you for your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information or other information. We also collect information about gift recipients so that we can fulfill the gift purchase. The information we collect about gift recipients is not used for marketing purposes. Like many websites, we use “cookies” to enhance your experience and gather information about visitors and visits to our websites. Please refer to the “Do we use ‘cookies’?” section below for information about cookies and how we use them.How do we use your information?Kushies Baby does not provide or sell your personal information for marketing purposes or any other purposes to other organizations/third parties, unless you have given us permission. We may use the information we collect from you when you subscribe to our newsletter, enter a contest or promotion, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways: To personalize your site experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested. To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests. To quickly process your transactions. To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature. Visitors who register or participate in other site features such as marketing programs and ‘members-only’ content will be given a choice whether they would like to be on our e-mail list and receive e-mail communications from us. We will respond to you only if you have requested us to do so and/or if we have collected your name, address, telephone number and/or email address.Kushies Baby Canada will disclose personal information and/or an IP address, when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to:1) Conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Floam ,2) Protect and defend the rights or property of Kushies Baby and related properties, or visitors to the Kushies Baby website or related properties.3) Identify persons who may be violating the law.4) Cooperate with the investigations of purported unlawful activities.How do we protect visitor information and your personal information?We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information. Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and is then encrypted into our databases to be accessed as stated above. SSL codes the information transferred between you and the server, rendering it unreadable to anyone trying to intercept the information. Any information disclosed from statistics is general and does in no way disclose personal identification details and it is for our use in identifying trends. Kushies Baby uses reasonable precautions to keep the information disclosed to us secure. We reserve the right to transfer all such information in connection with Kushies Baby’s assets. Furthermore, we are not responsible for any breach of security or for any actions of any third parties that receive the information. We are not responsible for such third party privacy policies or how they treat information about their users.Do we use “cookies”?Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site’s or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Chrom, Safari, or Firefox) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you turn cookies off, you won’t have access to many features that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone by contacting customer service.Third party linksIn an attempt to provide you with increased value, we may include third party links on our site. These linked sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We, therefore, have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these linked sites (including if a specific link does not work).Online Policy OnlyThis online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline. Changes to our Privacy Policy If our information practices change in the future, we will let you know by posting the policy changes on this website.
